0 Seconds to Destruction!
According to the Center of Astronomy and Space,
a meteor about 100 meters in size is in direct approach towards Earth.
At today's press conference, Mowtown's Mayor, Mr. Jacques
said that no damage is expected as the meteor will burn up in the atmosphere.
Anna, is that why your dad called you?
Yeah... he said it will be a rare sight in the sky,
so we should try not to miss it!
Glad it wasn't anything serious.
I was worried our cover was blown!
This is footage of the meteor captured by the Lunar Reconnaissance Orbiter.
That's...
What's wrong, Blue Cop?
That's not a meteor.
It's an escape pod from planet Machina.
Really?
I think you might be right.
I wonder who's on board?
Hope it's not another troublemaker like you!
What was that?!
Now is not the time to squabble.
If that's not a meteor...
Then that means it's not going to burn up in the atmosphere, and a giant hunk of metal 100 meters wide will crash straight into the Earth.
The entire town will be blown away without a trace!
What?!
But that means, if there's someone inside, can't you get them to stop or change their trajectory before that happens?
According to the news,
it will soon enter the Earth's orbit.
But there's no sign of it slowing down.
Oh no! Is the pod malfunctioning?
Or is the driver asleep at the wheel?
Oh, so you guys sleep too?
These guys even talk in their sleep and snore like crazy!
Look at this.
This is the drop point of the meteor according to an amateur astronomer.
It's in the middle of Mowtown!
The estimated time of impact is 2:51 PM.
We have less than two hours!
I'll ask my dad to issue an evacuation order right away!
But wait, Anna! What are you going to tell your dad?
That it's not a meteor, but a Metal Cardbot spaceship,
and it's about to crash into the Earth!
Even so, revealing all of this would be a problem.
Yeah! Who would even believe you?
They'll just say it's a tall tale and ignore it.
How about we think of a more effective plan?
What do you think we should do, then?
Just sit by and watch everyone in Mowtown disappear without a trace?
There's one thing that comes to my mind.
Do you think he'll believe us?
We don't have time to wonder! Let's hurry!
Anna and Theo have entered city hall, Jun.
Alright, Blue Cop! Come on home!
Roger that.
How's it going?
All done.
It's ready now.
There. We're connected to the satellite. Now we can communicate with the escape pod.
Wow, Uncle Edo! You're the best!
Stop calling me Uncle!
Ahem.
Attention escape pod! Decelerate immediately and prepare for landing!
I repeat! Decelerate immediately and prepare for landing!
An evacuation order?
That's not a meteorite! It's a spaceship from planet Machina-
No, Anna, you can't...
You said you were an amateur astronomer, right?
Could you explain to me what my daughter is trying to say?
My analysis results show that the meteor consists of Hafnium and Zirconium, along with other materials that make up the outer lining of space ships-
so there is concern that it will not burn up in the atmosphere, therefore crashing directly into the Earth!
Is this true?
I heard it from Blue Cop! So it must be true!
Blue Cop?
It's... the name of my friend's horse!
I don't get it. A horse told you?
No no no! It's the name of a kind robot called a Metal Cardbot.
What kind of joke is this?
Daddy!
This meteorite is being observed by the space institutes around the world,
So try not to worry! We don't want to cause widespread panic, right?
Anna!
Have a nice day!
How could he... he didn't even listen to a word I was saying!
Theo here. Mission failed.
We only have an hour left! Take Anna and go find shelter underground.
And the escape pod?
No word from it!
Are we even sure they're receiving our message?
It's a code used by all Metal Cardbots.
If they can't hear it...
Then their communicator might be broken!
In which case the pod will crash, and it will be over for all of us.
This can't be!
Isn't there anything else we can try?
Let's try sending a control protocol.
What's that?
It's a program that allows us to remotely control the escape pod.
We're connected.
I will change its course now.
Yes please!
The meteorite changed its course?
The space center reported that it seems to be accelerating, but the cause could not be confirmed.
Where is it going to fall?
Over there. That's the escape pod.
The drop point will be about 500 km southwest of Mowtown.
That is... above the ocean.
Then...
It's a success, Uncle Edo!
We did it, Jun!
Mayor Jacques held an emergency conference to announce that the meteorite approaching Earth
is falling into the sea about 500km southwest of Mowtown.
Haha, they did it Anna! The meteor changed its course-
Anna?
What? Anna?
Is that...
It's getting closer!
Hang on, I can't hear-
What... is that...?
Did they detach the escape pod?
Detach?
I think they took off a part of the pod to change its course.
What?!
Where is it falling now?
What?! Mowtown's residential area?!
Is anybody home?
Oh! So it was here!
It will land in about 10 more minutes.
Anna...
I need to get out of here!
Please, somebody help me!
Where could Anna be?
Found her!
Anna!
Mega Trucker, please help!
Leave it to me!
Anna!
Jun!
What are you doing here?
I left your birthday present behind.
Birthday present?
This isn't the time to be chatting.
10 minutes to impact.
We have to figure out a way to stop it!
With a few tweaks, I think I can make your shield even stronger.
Really? Then let's do it right now!
It's not that easy. The stronger the shield, the more energy it consumes, you know?
Your shield!
What about my shield?
Now's the time to combine everyone's strength!
This will sync your power generators.
Then, you can use Mega Trucker's shield to create a forcefield.
Great! Now be generous and send me all your energy till there's nothing left!
Do you really think you can handle all of our energy?
I wonder, what if it fails?
You can't think that way! I believe in you guys!
I know you will keep our town safe by working together!
If that's the case, looks like we'll have to give it a shot.
Y-Yes! Let's do our best!
I believe in you too.
Because Jun is my friend.
I believe in you too!
Thank you.
Now let's repay that trust!
Alright. Everyone, get ready!
Got it!
We're ready!
Okay!
Energy full charge!
Blue Cop?!
It's okay, Mega Trucker! I got your back!
I'll help, too!
-Me too!
-And me!
Guys! You got this!
Everyone, give it your all!
Ultra... Mega...
Power Shield!!
You did it...
Are you alright, Mega Trucker?
This is nothing! I'm fine!
Jun.
Anna...
I want you to know, I promise I'll keep the Metal Cardbots a secret.
Thank you, Anna. And...
I'm sorry I lied all this time.
No, no! I'm sure I would have done the same if I were you.